One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
you'll have to be tough.
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Landing on Fishman Island!
The Mermaid Cove and Gyoverly Hills!
What?!
Men!
For now, we shall retreat!
Yeah!
Roger that, Captain Vander Decken!
Angler! Wadatsumi! Pull the ship!
G-Gotcha!
This is terrible!
Luffy, tell the Kraken
to get us away from here as fast as possible!
Sure!
Hey, Surume!
Wait! That's not necessary!
He's already running for his life!
I never thought I'd see
a legendary beast reduced to this!
That's a big help! You're not so bad after all!
What a horrible way to run.
Don't say that!
That just shows how terrifying these eruptions are!
I'd really like to see an eruption!
Run to the front of the ship!
That won't help!
A few meters doesn't change anything!
The magma is flowing along the ocean floor!
The water temperature is rising!
It's like we're in a cooking pot!
Hot! Hot!
It's gonna start boiling!
The ghost ship and the Umibouzu!
Run, Surume!
The currents have started swirling
because of the temperature difference!
Nami-san.
Which way is Fishman Isl-
You're still having indecent thoughts, even now?!
We have to keep moving straight forward!
Just a little further!
Into that ocean trench!
A vertical drop! Are you serious?!
It's even darker than darkness!
Is Fishman Island really down there?!
It's so hot behind us! Too hot!
It's pitch black ahead of us! Scary!
It's obvious that there are even more monsters down there!
We'll never make it out alive!
Luffy! That darkness drops straight to hell,
it's like a bottomless pot!
Leap in!
Surume!
Another eruption!
What's that?!
Something's coming at us from above!
Boulders?!
A landslide?!
It's a rockfall! Look out!
It's collapsing because of the eruption just now!
Dodge them, Surume!
I'll leave the bubble and cut them down!
Luffy, hold on tight to me!
Sure, leave it to me!
Zoro, no!
Hey, let me go!
Why are you stopping him, Robin?!
We're 8 kilometers below the surface!
If you leave the bubble,
you'll be crushed by the water pressure!
Then what do we do?!
Deadly Green Star!
Sargasso!
Seaweed popped out!
The rockfall...
stopped!
That's amazing, Usopp!
That'll slow it down for a few seconds.
Get away from here while you have the chance, Surume!
We're safe!
Usopp, that was amazing!
Indeed, very quick thinking!
It was easy!
You saved us!
Surume! You did great!
Surume! Su-
10 kilometers below the surface: The Depths (Bottom of the trench)
W-We're safe.
Light? Even though we're this far below the surface?
It's so bright! My eyes are blinded...
Though I have no eyes that can be blinded.
Hey, you guys! Come and look at this!
Up there! Above us!
It's too bright. I can't see it very well.
Hey, Nami! Is that it?
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
The compass is pointing towards that island!
That's...
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's covered in an enormous bubble! And there are clouds on the inside?
Maybe there's air in there!
We did it! We're here!
One of the most famous spots on the Grand Line!
Oh, so we're here?
The island where the mermaids dance...
The beautiful mermaid princess...
Finally, I'm here! In the paradise I've dreamed of since I was a kid!
Mermaids! Mermai-
Sanji! It's hopeless!
Just imagining it caused him to become like this?!
I'm so sorry, Sanji!
I couldn't rehabilitate you in time!
It'd be better if you didn't meet the real mermaids.
Doctor! Meeting the mermaids of Fishman Island is his dream!
But if he meets them, he'll die!
Oh no!
I don't mind.
Sanji!
I don't want to live the rest of my life
without fulfilling this dream.
I'd rather see the mermaids and die from over-excitement!
You're the worst!
I will meet the mermaids!
I'm so excited! I wonder what sort of meat
they eat on Fishman Island?
Luffy, could you wipe that drool off your face
and ask Surume a favor?
Let's search for the entrance to Fishman Island.
Hey, what's with those guys?!
Who are they?!
It's a herd of sea monsters!
We're done for! And we made it so far!
These sea monsters are so...
cool!
Someone's riding them!
Why are you letting those humans boss you around...
Kraken?
What are you doing, Surume?! Carry us for the last stretch too!
You're the Straw Hat Crew, aren't you?
We know the name well...
You're the pirates who took out Arlong's crew.
If that's all you'd done,
our reaction would be obvious.
But of all things, two years ago you defended Hachi-san, a former member of Arlong's crew...
and from what I hear, you even beat up
one of those despicable Celestial Dragons!
Acts worthy of Fisher Tiger,
the hero of Fishman Island who we all admire!
New Fishman Pirates · Combatant
Hammond
I can't decide what to do with you.
Hey, tell me...
New Fishman Pirates · Hitman
Hyouzou
Are you friends, or foes?
I'll let you choose...
Will you join us, the New Fishman Pirates?
Or will you refuse us?
If you say no, we'll sink you right here and now.
What?!
Franky, refill the fuel.
Huh? What are you planning?
There's no way Luffy and the others will do what those guys say.
Even so, we're 10 kilometers underwater.
We can't even fight back down here. There's no chance of winning.
So let's flee!
We'll use up all the air left on the ship in one last Coup de Burst to charge straight toward the island!
Are you serious?!
It's either that, or we came all this way just to die.
True. I can't see any other way to survive this.
Right! I'll go fill up the fuel tanks!
Franky! You steer the ship!
You got it! I'll handle it superbly!
So, will you become our underling, Straw Hat Luffy?
No way.
Moron!
You refuse... You reject my invitation to join the New Fishman Pirates?!
In that case, you are enemies of the fishmen! Just a group of sinful humans!
Why should I have to be your underling?!
Luffy! You really shouldn't taunt them!
What a shame.
There's no way I can let you pass now.
Sea lion!
Energy Room
Franky, we're good to go!
You wanna fight?!
Do it, Franky!
The Sunny is a lion too!
Let's settle the score some other day, sea lion!
Here goes...
Coup de Burst!
Burst Blow
The ship...
The air... is disappearing!
I'm gonna be flattened...
Endure it! Until we break through to Fishman Island!
What is with that ship?!
We're breaking through!
Wait for me, my dear mermaids!
The coating came off!
It was absorbed by the giant bubble!
This bubble has two layers!
A normal ship would plummet to the bottom in this air-filled layer!
We're gonna use another Burst to get across!
Hold on tight!
Water...!
What a strong current!
Help me...
I can't breathe.
We've got four Devil Fruit users here!
Stretch out... your hands!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Dammit! I can't fight the current!
What a reckless way to enter the country... They might have killed themselves.
Wanna follow them, Hammond?
We can't be sure if they're dead or alive.
We should go, just in case.
I don't want the Neptune Army to find them before we do.
But first, let's return to the Noah, and inform the boss about this.
We should let him know that Straw Hat,
the one who shattered Arlong-san's ambitions, is here!
The Depths of Fishman Island
See?
Look!
I saw it!
I didn't see it!
Didn't you see it?
So what if I saw it?
See, he moved!
He moved!
He didn't move!
Didn't he move?
So what if he moved?
Alright! He's awake!
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
I'm so glad you're alright!
How do you feel?
If it isn't Caimie! It's been so long!
You're even cuter than you were
the last time I saw you, Caimie-chwan!
Have we arrived at Fishman Island?
Yeah! Apparently the mermaids saved us
when we were about to drown!
Indeed! There's no point in hiding it. We were all unconscious until now.
This is Caimie-chan's house.
Here, your hat.
Caimie's house, huh?
I'm sorry. I was planning to meet up with you,
but I didn't think you were coming until next month.
Don't sweat it! Where are the others?
Well... It appears we were separated.
I wonder if they're all okay?
Really?
Well, I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
Bones won't be much good in the water,
but they've got Robo and Green with them.
I'm sure they're fine.
I tried to reach them for as long as I could, but we were the only ones dragged to the bottom.
I really want to see the others soon.
Ah, here. You must be cold, right?
I made some soup, so drink up and get warm.
Ta-daah! Cold seaweed soup!
It's delicious.
Cold... soup?
Cold soup won't warm you up at all!
What am I going to do?!
I got it wrong!
It's fine, Caimie-chan.
On the contrary, it does warm me up!
What do you mean "On the contrary"?
H-Hey! Sanji, I want some too!
Your clothes are dry!
They're dry!
They're not dry yet!
Aren't they dry?
So what if they're dry?
You dried our clothes?
Thanks!
Thank you.
By the way, who are you guys?
Oh, they're my friends.
The Killifish Mermaid Quintuplets
I'm Ichika!
One-ka, Two-ka, Three-ka, Four-ka, and Four-ka Two
I'm Nika!
I'm Sanka!
I'm Yonka!
I'm Yonka Two!
Shouldn't that be Goka?!
Five-ka
They're fast swimmers, and quite well-informed too.
Oh, really?
This is the bottom of the Mermaid Bay.
We're in the ladies' dormitory of
the city's Mermaid Café, so I have lots of friends here.
L-Ladies' dormitory?!
It's the café where I work as a waitress.
There are plenty of beautiful mermaids there.
Sanji's...
in big trouble!
Like hell!
He's back!
I...
I swore that nosebleeds wouldn't make me
lose consciousness while I was on Fishman Island!
So please... Haven't I suffered enough?
You sure are serious about this.
I know, let's go upstairs!
I'll introduce you to my friends!
It's a turtle!
SEA
TURTLE
It says "Sea Turtle Elevator".
Turtle-chin. Take us up, please.
These are the underwater Coral Apartments.
My room is on the lowest floor, since it's the cheapest.
The highest levels, where the sun shines,
are the most expensive.
Are you poor?
By the way, what about Hachi and Pappagg?
Hacchin got badly injured about a year ago.
Yeah. He was protecting the Sunny
on the Sabaody Archipelago, wasn't he?
I heard that his injuries have more or less healed,
but Hacchin was originally a resident of
the Fishman District, so he's recovering there.
Fishman District?
It's kind of a scary place, but if you guys
are with me, I don't mind giving you a tour.
Let's go there after!
I have to meet Hachi and thank him, after all.
Sure, I got it.
Uh... And as for Pappagg...
He's a super-famous designer,
so he's got a huge mansion in Fishverly Hills, the most luxurious part of Fishman Island!
I'm going there to deliver clams for him today.
Why don't you come along?
Aren't you his owner?
Why don't you live together?
I don't really fit in there.
And the clams in these parts taste better anyway.
Hey, what's that straw-like thing?
Oh, that's...
the Water Road, created by
the bubble craftsmen of the island.
The fishes and merfolk like me ride it.
Just watch!
We've reached the surface!
Look! I can even swim through the sky!
That looks fun!
Huh?
Hey, wait! More importantly,
there are clouds and a sky here in the deep sea!
Hey, Caimie!
That was a woman's voice!
Everyone!
Are your friends alright now?
The pirates who drowned, I mean.
You're the ones who
didn't come through the entrance, right?
Hello. You don't look too scary.
Illegal immigrants? How wild! I really like pirates.
It's almost like a fairy tale world!
The coral continent! The mermaids' bay!
Sanji is sobbing?!
He's crying harder than he did when he left the Baratie.
I've finally found it!
This is my All Blue!
Are you really sure about that, Sanji?
I'll introduce them to you.
This is Luffy-chin, the captain!
The crying one is Sanji-chin!
And this is Usopp-chin with the nose!
Chopper-chin the raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Welcome! Let's dance together in the ocean!
Oh... I understand now.
There's no way such joy could exist.
I must have died today.
Negative!
Seriously, what happened to you during the past two years?!
This island is the paradise
you've always dreamed of, right?!
Sanji, you're so funny!
This barrel washed ashore with Caimie's friends.
I wonder what's inside it?
Alcohol? Treasure?
Who knows... It's sealed pretty tight, though.
What do you think? Should we secretly open it?
So Straw Hat Luffy...
has finally come here?
Fishman District "Noah"
Yeah...
W-What should we do, boss?
Bring him here... to me.